hancockwhitney.com 2018-09-27

# Privacy Policy | Hancock & Whitney Bank

 Rev 5/2018  
31400

**FACTS** | WHAT DOES HANCOCK WHITNEY CORPORATION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
---|---  
  **Why?** | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
---|---  
  **What?** | 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number and income
  * Credit history and credit scores
  * Account balances and payment history

---|---  
  **How?** | All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Hancock Whitney Corporation (HWC) chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
---|---  
  **Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does HWC share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes** — such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | YES | NO  
**For our marketing purposes** — to offer our products and services to you | YES | NO  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | YES | NO  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** — information about your transactions and experiences | YES | NO  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** — information about your creditworthiness | YES | YES  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | YES | YES  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** | NO | WE DON'T SHARE  
  **To limit our sharing:** | Call toll-free 888-416-4502. Our menu will prompt you through our choices.   
Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
---|---  
  **Questions?** | Call toll-free 888-416-4502 and press "0" to speak with a representative.  
---|---  
      **Who we are:**  
---  
  
**Who is providing this notice?**

| Hancock Whitney Corporation and its affiliates as defined below.  
  **What we do:**  
---  
  
**How does Hancock Whitney Corporation protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

We restrict access to confidential information to those employees who need to know such information to administer your account(s).  
  
**How does Hancock Whitney Corporation collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you:

  * Open an account or apply for a loan
  * Pay your bills or use your debit card
  * Show your drivers license

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

  * Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

| Your choices will apply to everyone on your account—unless you tell us otherwise.  
  **Definitions:**  
---  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * _Our affiliates include financial companies such as Hancock Whitney Bank and Hancock Whitney Investment Services, Inc._

**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * _Nonaffiliates we share with include companies such as direct marketing companies and check-printing companies._

**Joint marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * _• Our joint marketing partners include companies such as credit card companies and insurance companies._

## Online Privacy Policy
